A successful career
[music]
comes from relentless efforts
and endless passion
[music]
K
[music] [music]
[music]
I The long history
of the staff is young,
healthy and full of energy. I
immediately think of very
professional people in their work. They are
very professional, enthusiastic and
thoughtful in life, and also very
dynamic. They are very simple, very sincere, and
very dedicated. The
environment has given me a lot of
experience and made me more confident in my
work. Prudential employees are
enthusiastic, intelligent, dynamic, loyal
and professional. With
that work style, I will improve
myself a lot and learn a lot
from others. Brel is
a large university in the
insurance industry that has helped me
achieve dreams that
I almost thought I couldn't
achieve. Prudential people are a gathering of
talented people passionate about their work. There is something
very special about it: their spirit.  Team spirit,
that team spirit is
shown in difficult times. I am very
happy that I decided to
join Prudential right from the beginning of
2000 and until now, I have always strived
for the community, for the peace of mind and happiness of our
customers. The difference between Prudential
and other companies is the dedication
of our employees to customers, always
listening, always understanding,
ensuring that customers have access to the
best products available today. I have
worked with Prudential for almost 10 years and
I feel very happy to still be
working with you. I am very happy to
live in the same house with
all my colleagues. Be confident and do
your best, and all your wishes and dreams will come true.
Professionalism and
friendliness, even those who are not
professionals can become
professionals in a very
short time. Here, it's like a cradle
for career development.
For customers, we are a big family and
we are members of that family.
With unwavering passion...
The unity, passion, and growth create a
very friendly and
professional working environment. The
team's concerted effort and cooperation
allow everyone to fully develop their
abilities. I am very proud of working for PR.
I am standing on the shoulders of a
giant, a company with a strong brand and reputation.
My most profound memory with PR is
being caught speeding twice in one month, and
still having the same warning in the morning. It
seems to have become ingrained in everyone's blood
when working and dedicating themselves to creating
success for the organization. We are
a leading life insurance company in the
Vietnamese market, with a
very good cooperative and supportive attitude in our
work. We are diligent, hardworking, and even when tired,
we still smile. I am most satisfied with the
transfer of goods and services, and the Lien S is 100% accurate.
Actually, I probably don't have much to
say, I just want to hug all
my colleagues.
[Music]
aien
prenalen
prenalen toi Prudential
[Music]
toal chiến trc quan tâm sáng tạo hợp tác
Outstanding
[musical]
You are my crush